To access your Microsoft Office
programs on a Mac, there are
three ways you can do this.
First way is you can select the Finder.
And from there select Applications,
and then you can scroll down
to find the relevant program.
So Word, PowerPoint orExcel.
Alternatively, you can do your Launchpad
and on the Launchpad screen, you can then
navigate to where the program icons are,
which is Excel, PowerPoint, and Word.
And finally, you can attach the
shortcuts to the programs on your
tool bar at the bottom of the screen.
As you can see, I've placed Word,
Excel and PowerPoint on this bar
for easy access, which will then
automatically launch the programs.